Sena-chan, I'm sorry.
せなちゃん、ごめんなさい
It's like drinking strawberry jam.
なんかいちごジャム飲んでるみたいな
delicious?
美味しい?
delicious.
美味しい
You look cute today too.
今日も可愛いね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Sushi the other day.
この間、お寿司
how was it?
どうだった?
Was it delicious?
美味しかった?
Were you satisfied?
満足してくれた?
It was insanely delicious.
めちゃめちゃ美味しかった
Isn't it hot?
暑くない?
today.
今日
hot.
暑い
It was night the other day.
この間さ、夜だったじゃん
It's a blazer.
ブレザーでさ
At that time,
その時さ、
It was night.
夜 だったじゃん
It's noon today.
今日昼じゃん
It's kind of naughty.
なんか、エッチだね
picture?
え?
The front is important.
前は大事なんですよ
That's the back.
後ろがそう
The back is so emotional.
後ろがエモくて
What's behind?
後ろ何?
Show me a little.
ちょっと見せて
picture?
え?
what?
何?
terrible?
やばい?
Is he a dangerous person?
やばい人かな?
Lots of people pass by and you can see lots of things.
いっぱい人通っていっぱい見られる
She looks like a local woman.
地女みたいになってる
Come here for a moment.
ちょっとこっち来て
Today was the first time we met in a while.
今日はさ、 久々に会ったじゃん
I met you the other day, how was it?
この間さ、会ってさ、 どうだった?
good?
よかった?
good.
よかった
Were you spotted?
見ばれした?
I was spotted.
見ばれしました
What is that?
それは何?
High school friends?
高校の友達とか?
We became friends.
友達とかになれた
It was found out.
ばれちゃった
Even if it's ok.
まあまあでも
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
I'll do everything I can to support you.
サポートできる限りのことはちゃんとするから
Today, let's look at Sena's work.
今日はさ、 せなちゃんの作品見てさ、
People said it was a mess and that it was really cute.
めちゃくちゃさ、 すごい可愛いっていう声があったんだよね
So today, I would like to introduce people who want to
だから今日は、 やりたい人っていうのを、
I tried to collect a few.
ちょっと集めてみました
How many people?
何人か
何人か?
You've never done it, right?
やったことないでしょ?
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
ごめんごめんごめん
I felt a bit uneasy all of a sudden.
ちょっといきなりボクンだった
I tried to gather some people.
何人か集めてみました
It is played by multiple people.
それは、 複数人でのプレイ
That's right.
そうなんだよ
There are multiple people, right?
複数人ですよね
That's multiple people.
それが複数人なんですよ
To the first heart.
初の心に
That's right.
そうだよね
It's basic, after all, this kind of behavior is...
基本さ、やっぱさ、 こういう、 行為するのはさ、
It's one on one.
1対1じゃん
But today, by the way,
じゃなくて今日は、 ちなみにだけど、
I prepared for 3 people.
3人用意しました
3 people!?
3人!?
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
It's called 4P today.
いわゆる、 今日は4Pってやつ
Enough already.
もうもう
Today.
今日はね
It's called 4P.
いわゆる4Pって
I don't think there are many people who have experienced it.
なかなか経験してる人いないんじゃない?
There isn't one.
いないね
Moreover, I probably just graduated from high school.
しかも、 高校卒業したてで多分、
When it comes to raising children, well,
育ってやる子っていうのは、 まあ、
There isn't one.
いないね
Welcome.
いらっしゃいましょう
But now, I've already seen it, I've done it,
だけどさ、もうさ、見ばれさ、 しちゃってるしさ、
I want to hold it down a little, I don't want to be seen.
ちょっと押さえたいよね、見ばれはね
I want to suppress it, but the voice of the viewers is still there.
押さえたいけど、やっぱりさ、 視聴者さんの声がさ、
Please tease me a little more.
もうちょっといじめてくれよ
Did you have such an M feature?
そんなM機質ありました?
I.
私
No, please explain the situation.
いや、なんか、 状況してくれよ、
That's right.
だったりさ
Ah, I see.
あ、なるほど
That's what this is,
っていうのがさ、 こういうのが、
It's cute.
かわいいよ
How many times has this child come?
この子、 何回来てくださった?
That's it.
って
Maybe there were too many.
あまりにも多かったかもね
Call me midterm today.
今日中期呼び出して
Everyone, Ah, this is the reward.
みなさん、 あ、報酬これ
This is the reward.
報酬これ
That today.
今日それ
Well, it's new.
まあまあ、新作だから
Oh, just a moment on my chest, just a moment.
あれ、 ちょっと一回胸元、 ちょっと、
This, huh?
これ、 あれ?
Sena-chan, are you the type that shows off your eyes?
セナちゃんさ、 目映り激しいタイプなのかな?
The old man said he didn't know.
おじいさんの 知らないってなってさ、
I remember it being very clattery.
ガチャガチャした記憶あるんだけど
Kojikoji.
こじこじ
Yes, that's right.
ね、そうだよね
I'm not even in control of this right now, but
これは、ちょっと今、 お支配もしてないけど、
It's starting to look like this.
ちょっと なんか、 こっちに映り始めちゃってて
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
It's called Com Com Purin.
なかなかね、 コムコムプリンっていうんだけど、
I like what you say.
発言がいいのよ
Him too.
彼も
That's what it is.
そういうことね
I see.
そっか
なるほどね
Well, even if it's not particularly difficult,
じゃあ、 別にこじこじじゃなくても、
I think that's a push too.
そっちも押しだよっていうね
Yes, prevention.
そう、予防押し
That's true, but it's cute.
そうなんだけど、かわいいね
What is that?
それは何なの?
With Pechanrio's character.
ペシャンリオのキャラクターで
No, no, what is that?
違う違う、それは何?
Hairpins, bangs and main hair.
ヘアピン、前髪とメインを
hair clip.
ヘアクリップ
Everyone is doing it, I guess.
みんなやってるね、なんかね
Oh, I'm sure everyone is doing that.
あ、やってるわ、確かにみんなそれ
I have an image of a high school student.
高校生のイメージがある
My friends also put it on their bags.
友達とかもカバンにつけたりしてる
That's right, in the background.
そうだよね、バックでね
That's what it is.
そういうことね
Well then, next time, maybe again.
じゃあ、今度はじゃあ、 もしまたね、
Next time I have to take a photo shoot, I'll be like this,
今度撮影ってなったら、 このガチャガチャじゃ、
I have to do Pon Pon Purin too.
ポンポンプリンもやらないとね
What will you do if you get stuck next time?
次こじこじついてたらどうする?
Both.
どっちも
Should I wear both?
両方つける?
I think I added both.
両方つけた気がする
I might be pretty excited.
結構ワクワクにしてるかも
Are you nervous?
緊張は?
I haven't.
してない
Shall we meet once?
一回じゃあ顔合わせする?
I'll be here in a little while.
もうちょっとで来るからさ
I'll be here in a little while, so let's meet once,
もうちょっとで来るから、 一回顔合わせして、
Let's do an uplay of that, Pon Pon Purin.
そのアップレイしちゃおうか、 ポンポンプリンってね
Today is short again.
今日さ、 短いじゃん、また
short?
短い?
Isn't it shorter than before?
今までより短いんじゃないの?
Hey, can you sit down for a second?
ちょっとさ、 ちょっと座る?
Come here for a moment.
ちょっとおいでこっち
There are a lot of people here, aren't there?
ちょっとこっちさ、人いっぱいいんじゃ?
There is.
いる
many people
多い人
but.
が
Please sit there for a while.
そ こちょっと座ってもらって
Can you sit down?
座れる?
Good shots!
よいしょっと!
My face isn't shown.
顔が映してない
It's white today too.
白だね、今日も
It's white.
白です
I understand.
よくわかりです
It was white the other day.
この間も白だったもんね
white.
白
I think it's still a little early for flashy dolls.
まだ派手な人形はちょっと早いかな
early?
早い?
I feel like I can't go on an adventure yet.
まだちょっと冒険できないなって思う
That's right.
そうだよね
It suits you.
似合うね
still?
まだ?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Is it okay to have self-produced rights?
自作権とか大丈夫?
perhaps.
多分
Wait a minute.
ちょっと待ってね
Sorry.
ごめんね
Strong local woman taste.
地女味強い
Earthy and feminine?
地女味?
Earth girl.
地女
Well then, Jijo.
じゃあ地女
I mean, I'm a local woman, but I'm forced to do it.
地女っていうか、やらされてるけどね
Completely.
完全に
I might be able to achieve something like walking without blades someday.
そのうちノーブレード散歩とか成就できるかもしれない
Wow, can I have that?
うわ、それもらっていい?
On the contrary.
逆にね
Can I have some of that?
それちょっともらっていい?
That's a little bit.
それちょっと
Are you serious?
マジかい
I really want that, right now.
それさ、ガチで欲しいんだけど今
What is that?
何それ?
I want it now.
今欲しいんだけど
It goes around for about 5 minutes?
5分ぐらい一周回る?
I'll try going around.
回ってみます
I feel like I gave a crappy service.
めちゃめちゃサービスしちゃったな気がします
I agree.
そうだね
This is the morning of a sudden hug.
これさ、いきなりハグの朝
Hey, that's it.
ちょっと あれじゃん
Should I go once in the dark?
一回暗闇行く?
No blade.
ノーブレード
I shouldn't have said that.
言わなきゃよかったね
I thought that was really good, and...
俺はそれ、マジでいいと思って、 ちょっと、
I got it.
もらっちゃった
I was the one whose world came out.
私たちのワールドが出てきてしまったのが自分だった
I agree.
そうだね
I just got that.
ちょっとそれもらっちゃったわ
That made me panic.
慌ててもらっちゃったわ、それ
I guess I'll take that with me for now.
と りあえず、それ持っとこうか
I guess I'll just keep that for now.
とりあえず、それ持っとこうか
It's no blade.
ノーブレードですね
Machine-kun’s low pants?
マシン君のローパン?
He will do it for you.
やってくれるんですよ
picture?
え?
You're taking it too seriously, aren't you?
本気にしすぎでしょ
For now, do you want the top?
とりあえず、上欲しい?
superior?
上?
Wait a minute, then.
ちょっと、じゃあ
Okay.
よーし
I feel like it's over.
終わってみたいな
It doesn't make sense, does it?
意味ないでしょ
Lie, really?
嘘、本当に?
I'll show you somewhere.
どっかで見せる
Just a stop for now.
今のところ、ちょっとストップ
It's a stop.
スト ップ です
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Stop for a moment.
ちょっと、ストップで
This person and this person went.
この人と、 この人、行きました
I can go for about 5 seconds.
5秒ぐらい、行ける
Poctor.
ポクトル
Can you go?
行ける?
Nice.
ナイスネース
Highest.
最高
I took it off.
僕、外しちゃいました
This and a dress shirt.
これと、ワイシャツ
Let's talk about the shirt.
ワイシャツのこと、出しちゃえ
Oh, look, there's a string.
え、だってほら、ひもが
picture?
え?
Okay, let's lift it.
じゃあ、持ち上げる
Can I hit it once?
一回、打ていい?
I don't even put my arms out.
腕も出さない
Hey, my, are you okay?
ちょっと、私の、 大丈夫ですか?
Compra.
コンプラでね
Um, I don't really care about Compra.
あの、 コンプラ、あんまり気にしないけど
Now, now, pretty-chan.
今ね、今、結構ちゃん
Yes, this person went.
うん、この人、行きました
Aren't only girls good at that kind of thing?
女の子だけ、そういうの、得意じゃない?
Stop for a moment.
ちょっと、ストップです
OK.
OKです
Now it's perfect.
今、完璧です
One chan, it might be impossible.
ワンチャン、無理かもしれない
One chan, impossible?
ワンチャン、無理?
One chan, is it impossible?
ワンチャン、無理か
It's not on.
ついてない
Because it's not here.
ここが無いから
What, what is that sound?
え、何、その音が?
What do you mean?
どういうこと?
It's kind of unique.
なんか、独特なんですよ
Is that so?
そうなの?
Isn't this the one on the shoulder?
こういう、肩のやつじゃない?
yes.
そう
How do I wipe it?
どうやって、拭くの?
that.
それ
How do you put it on?
どうやって、つけんの?
I don't wipe it.
拭かない
Why don't you wipe it?
拭かないか
I want to push Lambreau.
ランブルオさんとか、押したい
Hey, I want some pants.
ちょっと、パンツ、欲しいな
He was saying something.
なんか、言ってました
I said something.
なんか、 言 って ました
Well then, I want some pants.
じゃあ、パンツ、欲しいな
If it were pants, that would be weird.
パンツだったらさ、だってさ、変な話さ
Just pull it out.
ちょっと、抜くだけじゃん
It's a little bit.
ちょっとじゃん
Stop now.
今、ストップです
Absolutely dangerous.
絶対、ヤバい
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
shoulder side, shoulder side.
肩側、肩側
30 seconds, 30 seconds.
30秒、30秒
Only 30 seconds.
30秒だけ
Now, now, now.
今、今、今
Now, 30 seconds.
今、30秒
Take off your pants.
パンツ、抜けよ
Just keep it hidden.
隠しといてね、ちゃんと
Be sure to hide it.
絶対、隠しといてね
It really smells like nothing I said.
めちゃくちゃ、言ってない匂いするんじゃん
It's really not painful.
めちゃくちゃ、苦しない
worst.
最悪
By the way, what kind of pants did you wear?
ちなみにさ、 ちなみにさ、 どういうパンツしたのか、
Look.
見て
Why, no.
なんで、だめだ
Give it back, give it back.
返して、返して
I understand, I understand.
分かった、分かった
Keep it safe.
ちゃんと持っておく
By fortune telling.
占いで
Keep it safe.
ちゃんと持っておく
I put it in my pocket right now.
ちゃんと今、ポケットにしまったから
Are you going back?
帰座る?
Go back and sit down.
帰座ってみ
Convenience store, near my house, To go to a convenience store, etc.
コンビニ、家の近く、 コンビニとか行くのには、
How many times did we go together?
僕らで行くことは何回だった?
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
I kind of get it.
なんかね、分かる
Ah, I can see that this person is a nobleman.
あ、この人、ノブレなんだって、分かる
lie?
嘘?
Are you looking at that much?
そんなに見てる?
everyone.
みんな
You'll see it.
見るよね
I'll take a look too.
俺も見ちゃうもん
With the toy lights, a beautiful lady, etc.
トイス明かりでさ、 きれいなお姉さんとかさ、
I'll go to the convenience store.
コンビニで行くじゃん
I keep looking at her chest.
胸元ばっかり見ちゃう
It's not the butt.
お尻じゃない
I'll see your butt too.
お尻も見るよ
I see, then how about we take a little walk?
そっか、じゃあちょっと散歩する?
Does it sizzle?
スースーするの?
Isn't it dangerous from behind?
するし、なんか後ろ危ないんじゃない?
Look.
ほら
Just a little bit,
ちょっとさ、
Just go over there.
もう ちょいあっち行って
Um, let's spread out the skirt a little.
あの、スカートをさ、 ちょっと散らって、
I wish you could turn it over,
めくってほしいなと思うんだけど、
Wait a minute.
ちょっと待つね
I want you to come here a little more.
もうちょっとこっち来てほしいな
I'll take a good look at it.
ちゃんと見とくから
There are lots of hand photos.
手撮りいっぱいあるね
It's cute.
可愛いね
I like your breasts.
このあなたのおっぱいって私、 好きです
a,
あ、
Give it to me now.
今 ちょうだい
今ちょうだい
Scattered.
散らって
picture?
え?
Are you there?
いる?
there was.
いた
there was?
いた?
sorry.
ごめん
So, if we do it optimally, can we go here or there?
じゃあ、 最適にそしたら、 こっちあっちに行ける?
Next time, I want the rear version.
今度、じゃあ後ろバージョンほしいな
Wait a minute.
ちょっと待ってね
It's still stopped.
まだストップです
Please come over here for a moment.
もうちょっとこっち来てもらって
Not yet.
まだだよ
Oh, turn around.
あ、後ろ向いて
Oh, please.
あ、ください
Oh, that, that, that.
あ、それそれそれそれ
Erotic.
エロ
picture?
え?
Shall I meet you face to face?
私、顔合わせしようか
But that wasn't the plan.
だけど、 そういう企画じゃなかったんよね
What is the main thing?
メインは?
That was the main thing.
メインはそうだったじゃん
There wasn't anything like that though.
そういうあれはなかったんだけど
What is this concentrated play?
なにこの集中プレイ
Sometimes.
たまにはさ
It's good once in a while.
たまにはいい
Well then, let's meet for a while and fly away.
じゃあちょっと顔合わせして、 飛んで、
Well then, let's go for a while, for now.
じゃあちょっと 行こっか、とりあえずね
Well then, let's continue inside the hotel.
じゃあ今度また続きホテルの中で
good?
いい?
Stroll through Nobra Knit.
ノブラニットを散歩
It was fun.
楽しかったね
Then, let's go to the next hotel.
じゃあ 次ホテルね
Seno-chan?
瀬野ちゃん?
You came to the hotel.
ホテル来たね
I have come.
来 ました
Were you nervous to meet face to face?
顔合わせ緊張した?
It makes me nervous.
緊張するよね
As expected.
さすがにね
Moreover, after being made to do such a thing,
しかもあんなことさせられてからの、
Nice to meet you.
はじめましてで
Actually, when I come to the hotel like this, the atmosphere comes out again.
実際こうやってホテル来たら、 ちょっと雰囲気また出てくるで
Sho.
しょ
So I made sure to wear pants.
だから ちゃんとパンツは履かした
As expected.
さすがにね
Hello, I'm wearing no panties.
さすがにノーパンで、こんにちは、
Just a little.
ちょっとさ
It's going to feel like,
っていう感じになっちゃうじゃん、
on second thoughts.
やっぱり
Wait a minute, okay?
ちょっとじゃあ、いいですか?
You're wearing them properly.
ちゃんと履いてるね
I'm wearing them.
履いてます
That's how I explained the plan.
そういうことで、 企画説明したじゃん
Just to confirm, are you okay?
確認だけどさ、 大丈夫?
it's okay.
大丈夫です
If you've come this far, all I can say is that it's okay.
ここまで来たら大丈夫しか言えないよね
By the way, you said you've never done it.
ちなみにさ、 やったことないって言ってたじゃん
He said there was no play like that.
そういうプレイないって言ってたじゃん
Well, I'm not going to do it anyway.
なんかその、 どうせさ、やるわけじゃん、
from now.
今から
I feel like I want to play something like this.
なんかこういうプレイしたいな、だったりさ
Is there something like that?
なんかそういうのある?
I'm quite M, so it's more than M.
私結構Mなんで、 Mよりなんで
I'm really happy though.
めっちゃ嬉しいけど
It's like I want to be bullied.
いじめられたいみたいな
Well then, it seems like you want to be gently teased a little.
じゃあ優しくちょっといじめられたいみたいな
Be kind.
優しめに
優しめにね
That's how it is.
そんな感じでじゃあ
yes.
はい
good?
いい?
it's okay.
大丈夫です
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
You look a little scared.
ちょっと顔、怖まってるね
I'm really nervous.
めっちゃ緊張します
Isn't it cute?
可愛くない?
How to sit.
座り方
Well, I was told to sit like this.
え、なんかこうやって座りって言われました
Seriously?
マジで?
what?
何?
To a high school teacher?
高校の先生に?
This is how girls should sit.
こうやって女の子は座りなさいと
I absolutely hate it when this happens.
こうしたら絶対嫌って
Is that so?
そうなの?
Isn't your body too soft?
体柔らかすぎない?
I think I hate it.
嫌って思う
There's nothing wrong with girls.
女の子は何もいけない
I don't know.
分かんない
There's something about me in the picture.
なんか私が映ってる
Just like before.
持って前みたいに
Again?
またですか?
I'll make you do this again.
またやらせるんですね、これ
I just fell in love with that.
さっきハマってんだよ、それ
Is this it?
これですか?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
This is showing properly.
ちゃんと映ってますよ、これ
It's beautiful.
きれいですね
amazing.
すごい
I'm not old enough to have pores, pores.
毛 穴、毛穴っていう歳じゃないじゃん
Sena-chan.
セナちゃんはさ
I recently left because I ate too much sweets.
最近 お菓子食べすぎて離れた
I'm 18 and eat sweets, that's it.
18歳お菓子食べるよ、それ
I ate too much sweets and left.
お菓子食べすぎて離れた
I only eat sweets.
お菓子ばっかり食べるよ
I'm eating something sweet.
甘いもの食べてる
Well, today was mackerel.
じゃあ、今日はサバだったじゃん
It was mackerel.
サバだった
There was sushi last time.
前回あるじゃん、お寿司じゃん
Sushi.
お寿司
So today we're going to have some sweets.
じゃあ、今日はお菓子ということで
It's gradually going down a bit.
だんだんちょっと下がっていくけど
surely.
確かに
Today's topic is sweets.
今日はお菓子ということでね
Is it time to get rid of your tight lips?
そろそろくっちゃびりはもういい?
yes.
はい
Shall we go? It's about time.
行きますか、そろそろ
It's okay now.
もう大丈夫よ
It makes me a little nervous.
ちょっと緊張するよね
I'm really nervous.
めちゃめちゃ緊張してる
There are so many things I really want to do today.
いっぱい今日、本当にやりたいって
It was there just now.
さっきもいたじゃん
We gathered people who saw Sena's work and wanted to do it.
セナちゃんの作品見て、やりたいよっていう人を集めました、
Because it's like that.
みたいな感じだから
yes.
はい
So-called fans.
いわゆるファン
What is a fan?
ファンって?
Yeah, I thought I wouldn't be left behind.
うん、押し残らんと思って
Understood.
分かりました
OK
Fans, yes, I understand.
ファン、はい、分かります
It's like a fan appreciation party.
ファン感謝祭みたいな
It's too Thanksgiving though.
感謝祭すぎますけど
It's not often that I can cry.
泣けるなんてなかなかないですよね
Well then, let's do it.
じゃあ、やっていこうか
copper?
どう?
Let's look forward to this a lot.
この、いっぱい期待しよう
That's terrible.
やばいですね
terrible.
やばい
copper?
どう?
Like this image of hell.
この地獄映像みたいな
Look, you can see it.
見て、見えるでしょ
What do you think of this video?
この映像どう?
That's terrible.
やばいですね
It's too much of an experience for the first time, isn't it?
初めても経験すぎるでしょ
It's too early.
初めてすぎる
I'm a little nervous.
ちょっと緊張がやばいです
Sena-chan said that she wanted to stay behind,
セナちゃん押し残って言ってたけど、
He's a pushy old man.
押しのおじさんです
That's not true.
そのことないです
Fan Thanksgiving.
ファン感謝祭
Thanksgiving.
感謝祭
What will Sena-chan do for you?
セナちゃん何をしてくれるの?
I will serve you.
ご奉仕します
I will do my best.
頑張ります
Service?
ご奉仕?
specifically.
具体的に
I've only been asked about my face.
ちょっと顔しか聞いてきてない
I just asked you to come anyway, so I came today.
とにかく来てくれってだけ言われて今日来たから
today?
今日?
It was just called a fan appreciation festival.
ファン感謝祭ってだけ言われてきてたから
What happened?
何 かなって
I will do what I can't do.
行けないことはします
I was teaching you a little more.
もうちょっと教えてたから
What do you do?
何をするの?
I won't let you know.
知 らせない
Did you like Shirashippu?
知らしっぷで好きだったの?
What do you do?
何をするの?
What do you make?
何を作るの?
What are you going to make?
何を作るんですかね?
If you don't tell me Sena-chan, I'll ask you if you like me.
セナちゃん教えてくれないと、俺は好きかって言っちゃうけど
good?
いい?
I'll do whatever I want.
欲 望のままにやっちゃうから
that's right.
そうです
be.
ある
You can also finish it as you like.
勝手に仕上げも
If you didn't tell me.
教 えてくれなかったら
This is how you sit, as I mentioned earlier.
座り方はこれでさっき言ってましたけど、
When I start from here, I stand for a while and finish the work.
こっちからやってると、 ちょっと 立って仕上げも
Is this better?
こっちの方がいいのかな?
Well, let's finish it.
じゃあ、仕上げても
yes.
はい
Let's get started.
始 めちゃうもん
At first, everyone's breathing became less and less unpleasant.
最初もみんな、どんどん鼻息悪くなくしちゃったもん
Try this for yourself.
ちょっと自分でこれしてみて
By yourself?
自分で?
Do you usually do it yourself?
普段自分でするの?
Yeah.
うん
I cheated.
ずるんだ
It was speed, now.
速度だったね、今
It was really fast.
めっちゃ速かったね
That's right.
そうなんだ
I have to make that face.
そこの顔しないと
Sena-chan looks serious.
セナちゃん、真剣そうだわ
Even though it's lustful.
欲的なのに
You're so excited, Sena-chan.
ノリノリだね、セナちゃん
As expected, it's bread thanksgiving.
さすがパン感謝祭だね
Stop it.
やめて
Shall I take off my pants?
パンツ脱いちゃおうか
Is there such a thing?
そんなことある?
I feel grateful.
ありがたい感じ
a little bit.
ちょっと
Don't hide it, spread it out and show it to me.
隠すんじゃなくて、自分で広げて見せてあげて
Don't hide it.
隠すんじゃなくて
Are you expanding it?
広げてる?
They told me it wouldn't spread.
これで広がらないと言ってくれたよ
Take a little drive.
ちょっとドライブ
Did you go as you came?
来るまま行った?
Haven't you been there?
行ってなかったの?
No good, right?
ダメでしょ?
Didn't you tell me?
言ってなかったの?
sorry.
ごめんなさい
It's Thanksgiving, but are you being punished?
感謝祭だけど、お仕置きされてる?
Maybe it's better that way.
もしかしたらそっちの方が
That's right.
そうなんだ
sorry.
ごめんなさい
Finished.
お仕上がり
It's a little fun.
ちょっと楽しい
copper?
どう?
Who is this fan?
このファンの人は?
What about this fan?
このファンの人はどうですか?
fine?
元気?
Yeah.
うん
Yeah?
うん?
Does it feel good?
いい感じ?
Yeah.
うん
Was it delicious?
美味しかった?
Yeah.
うん
Small.
ちっちゃい
Your mouth is a bit boring.
ちょっとお口が、 退屈だね
Isn't it boring?
退屈じゃない?
My mouth...
口が...
Can I say that my mouth is noisy?
口がうるすって言えばいいかな?
Let me just shut my mouth for a moment.
ちょっと そんな、 口塞いでもらおうか